nice to meet you.
初めまして
It's really cute.
め っちゃ可愛いですね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Are you a little nervous?
ちょっと緊張してる?
Just relax.
ちょっとリラックスして
What do you usually do?
いつも何してるの?
I always go to school.
いつも学校行ってます
Are you going to school?
学校行ってるんだ?
What are your hobbies?
趣味とかは何?
shopping.
買い物
Are you going with friends?
友達と行くの?
Alone.
一人で
Are you going alone?
一人で行くんだ?
Do you have any other hobbies?
他に何か趣味ある?
I'm going to a cafe.
カフェ行く
With friends.
友達と
That's fine.
そういうのはいいんだ
What do you eat at the cafe?
カフェでどんなの食べるの?
Or Austanbul tea.
アウスタンブルティーとか
What is your favorite food?
好きな食べ物は何?
strawberry.
イチゴ
You seem to like it.
好きそうだね
Do you have a boyfriend now?
今、彼氏はいるの?
not present.
いない
Isn't it delicious?
美味しくない?
delicious.
美味しい
degree
ど
Do you like Itchi?
んな イッチが好きとかある?
Does it feel like flirting?
イチャイチャする感じかな?
Feeling like flirting?
イチャイチャする感じ?
What is your favorite Thailand?
好きなタイは?
Top.
上位
Try reaching over there and sticking your butt out.
向こうに手ついて、 お尻を突き出してみて
Sit down again.
また座って
A pleasant face.
気持ちいい顔
Because it looks good in style.
スタイル良さそうだから
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよね
not at all.
全然
I can't see it even though I can see it.
見えそうで見えない
Even just a little bit sticks out.
ちょっとだけでもはみ出てるよ
I'm feeling crunchy.
コリコリしてるよ
The style is quite good.
ス タイル相当いい
That's a cute sneeze.
かわいいくしゃみだね
I can see the soles of your feet.
足の裏見られてるよ
The soles of your feet?
足の裏?